<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>recruiting | Zeyu Wang</title>
    <link>https://zw615.github.io/categories/recruiting/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://zw615.github.io/categories/recruiting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>recruiting</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:40:25 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://zw615.github.io/images/icon_hu47e97d5e8666104847c7243b60de4ed2_370712_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>recruiting</title>
      <link>https://zw615.github.io/categories/recruiting/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Recruiting PhD students</title>
      <link>https://zw615.github.io/post/recruiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 13:40:25 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zw615.github.io/post/recruiting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am seeking creative, hard-working, PhD students (and master&amp;rsquo;s students
and undergraduates) to join the XAI group at UCSC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Come work with me on making complex mechanisms more understandable for
debugging and diagnosis, accountability, and liability.  We examine
applications in autonomous driving, deep learning, and other
mission-critical or safety-critical applications.  Additionally, my
work also examines the role of explanations for trustworthy ML,
human-machine teams, AI and ethics, and AI safety and fairness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ucsc-undergrad&#34;&gt;UCSC undergrad&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UCSC undergraduates are welcome to contact me about getting involved
in research. Students interested in joining the group should have
basic programming experience, and preferably, have taken CSE 140.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;ucsc-master-s-students&#34;&gt;UCSC Master&amp;rsquo;s students&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current UCSC Master&amp;rsquo;s students interested in gaining research
experience or looking for a supervisor for a research project may
contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In your introductory email, please include a CV/resume, and indicate a
few topics or application domains of interest.  I&amp;rsquo;ve listed a couple
ongoing projects on the 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://grad.soe.ucsc.edu/cse/masters_projects&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;UCSC CSE master&amp;rsquo;s board&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;prospective-phd-students&#34;&gt;Prospective PhD students&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m currently looking to build the XAI group with driven, hard-working
PhD students.  Students will work on various projects with a focus on
autonomous systems, robust machine learning, and/or explainability and
interpretability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In your introductory email, please include a CV/resume, and indicate a
few topics or application domains of interest.  (For inspiration, some ongoing projects
are listed 
&lt;a href=&#34;../..#projects&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but feel free to define your own!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;before-contacting&#34;&gt;Before contacting&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prospective PhD students, please review the UC Santa Cruz CSE 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://grad.soe.ucsc.edu/cse&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PhD
admissions requirements&lt;/a&gt; and ensure
that you meet these requirements &lt;strong&gt;before contacting&lt;/strong&gt;
Prof. Gilpin. (Note: the GRE is no longer required!)  I can only take
on students that are accepted to a PhD program at UCSC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m unable to provide insights about admissions decisions.  The
admission decisions are made by a committee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;diversity-statement&#34;&gt;Diversity statement&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Explanatory AI is an interdisciplinary field which benefits from the
perspectives and contributions of those from diverse voices (diversity
broadly defined).  We encourage anyone who shares our interests,
including members of historically underrepresented and marginalized
groups, women, LGBTQ+ folks, and people with disabilities (with
diversity broadly defined), to consider joining us at UC Santa Cruz!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
